ILR School School Scrapbook /3069
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School School Scrapbook
1945-1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/3069
4.67 cubic feet
3.7 linear ft.
Scrapbooks.
Consists mainly of news clippings and press releases.
8436564
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, October 29, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 13, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Administration
8436564
- Newspapers (Bound), 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- The I.L.R. Scrapbook, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Public Relations Scrapbook May 1, 1953 - Apr. 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Jan. 1961 - Jan. 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR School April 1954, May 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- January 1962 to January 1964, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- News Clippings Sept. 1952 - April 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- March. 1955 - Feb. 1956, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ILR Press Cliffings April 1960 - April 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Press Releases May 1957 to Oct. 15, 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Scrapbook 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Press Releases Feb. 1956 to May 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILR School Clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- May - 1949 - Jan. 1956, 1949-1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- News Clippings December 1949 - July 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- News clippings ILR School January 1952 - August, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- ILR Scrapbook August 1950 - February 1951, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- School Press Releases Feb. 1946 - Sept. 1947, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- News clippings - ILR School -- March-October, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- News clippings - ILR School -- October 1951-January 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)